I don't remember where my house is.
Take me to Yoo Jung.
Yoo Jung's worried about you. Get in the car.
You still remember that?
Of course.
You thought I don't know that you make Yoo Jung your scapegoat?
Driver!
Kang Yoo Jung!
What are you doing?
What are you doing here at this time?
What's going on, Do Hoon?
- I'll make some tea. - Wait!
Can you stay like this for a moment?
I'm sorry.
You tend to come to others' house a lot.
- I'm sorry. - What now?
I'm sorry you had to see me like this.
I'm not the only one who's lost a loved one.
My father and San are gone.
I hate myself for being alive like this.
I think I know how much you hate me.
At least you know.
You helped me keep going.
I didn't have the courage to kill myself...
So I found you and complained about you, and then I get through it.
Look at me and get through it.
What makes you so upset?
People.
I became a prosecutor while others made sacrifices.
I get this high by my own efforts.
But there are always people born above me.
I have abandoned everything to make this high,
the people who makde sacrifices have put obstacle in my way.
People of higher status are not that comfortable as well.
You might think that I'm being whiny,
but I gave up a lot of things to meet my parents' expectations.
- If you knew that... - I know. We both gave up something,
but what we had at the beginning were different.
Has the world ever been equal?
Never.
However, if you waste your time complaining,
you're a foolish man.
Thank you for your advice.
This is not advice.
I'm trying to encourage you not to give up.
Yoo Jung! Hey!
Hi!
- We have to go to check the shopping mall. - I know.
Kwang Soo, how do you think she is?
- What? Has something happened? - Nothing.
Let's go.
This is my day off. How could you do this to me?
Hae Ri, just for today.
When you need a day off, I'll fill in for you.
What happened? You look terrible.
You didn't even come home last night.
Never mind. I have to go.
Thank you.
Let's go back. I'm worried about Yoo Jung.
What happened?
She's acting like nothing happened.
It's even worse.
I've seen people like her before.
It makes me worried. Turn the car around.
Yes, sir.
Manager!
- Yes, sir. - Hello.
I don't see Kang Yoo Jung.
She said she has somethign urgent to do, so she switched with Hae Ri.
Where is Kang Yoo Jung?
Well, I don't know.
How come you don't know?
I asked her, but she didn't answer.
She just asked me to change shift with her.
This is our phone number right here.
When a patient is missing,
whoever finds him, will contact us.
My father was wearing this as well,
but it went missing.
He couldn't take it off on his own.
Look at this.
Can you check if anyone called?
If anyone had, we would've called you.
His contact is Mr. Ahn Do Hoon. Is that correct?
I'll be right up.
Okay.
What do you want?
We're not supposed to meet again.
I do. Come with me.
I'm busy. I have a meeting.
This is more urgent. Come with me.
Sir! Are you okay?
We need to talk.
Get her out of here.
Do Hoon!
Now!
Do Hoon! Do Hoon...
Do Hoon! Do Hoon!
Do Hoon! Do Hoon! Let me go.
She's not here. Why can't you trust me?
Where is she, then?
That's what I want to ask you.
She hasn't come home for 2 days.
What happened to her?
You must know where she is.
I guess something happened and she wants to hide herself.
She's been in a mess, why can't you leave her alone?
What do you want?
When I found my father in Pohang,
the bracelet was missing.
I mean his bracelet.
You said he couldn't take it off on his own.
Why are you telling me this?
Because you saw my father on that day.
Didn't you?
Yes, I did.
I put him in the car,
but he was struggling to get out.
It was too dangerous, so I pulled over.
And he ran away.
You're lying.
It was raining and there were too many people to find him.
Are you trying to blame me?
You're lying.
So what?
What if I really abandoned your father in the wilderness?
It's you who didn't take care of him.
It's you who didn't listen to me to send him to sanatorium.
Your stubbornness made this happen.
My father trusted you.
I know. I was sick of it.
I didn't continute to find him, so what?
Stop the car!
I told you to stop the car.
Are you crazy?
It could've caused an accident.
Why did you do that?
How could you do this to me?
How could you?
To me and my father?
Were you sick of San?
Is that why you took him?
You took him away,
and let him die just like that?
What?
You're completely out of your mind.
Get out! Get out!
How can I possibly not go insane?
How can you be sane?
Kneel down!
Apologize to San and my father.
Kneel down and beg for forgiveneess.
If I kneel down and apologize,
will you disappear forever?
I don't want to look back on the past.
You're always there.
And you keep on holding me back.
Hold you back?
I said
I'd make you happy.
I was being arrogant.
You said you wouldn't regret it.
I'm regretting it.
When you decided to go to jail for me,
if I abandoned you at that time,
we wouldn't have come this far.
You'll regret it from now on.
I'll tear you apart and make your life a living hell.
Wait and see.
You'll never forget me, San,
and my father who treated you as his own son.
I won't let you forget.
You want me to disappear?
Not a chance!
I'll follow you wherever you go.
You'll see me everywhere.
Don't even think about running away.
Why do you come to me?
I want to stay with you.
Why?
I have something to do.
Something I must do.
Do you think that I'll help you without knowing what's going on?
As you wish, I'll lead an unhappy life.
I'll live the most miserable life.
Please.
Why should I help you?
Is it because of Ahn Do Hoon?
You tried to protect at the risk of your life last time,
why the sudden change of heart?
It's the only thing I can do for the people I've lost.
I can't get back what he took from me,
but I can take what's his.
I'll tear you apart and make your life a living hell.
- Say thank you. - Watch me.
I won't let you forget me,
- San, and my father who treated you as his own son. - Father.
You shouldn't do that. Do Hoon.
I'll follow you wherever you go.
You'll see me everywhere.
I won't regret it. I won't look back on the past, Yoo Jung!
I want to destroy Ahn Do Hoon as well.
That's not diffcult.
Should I take everything away from him?
I can kick him out of the K Corporation.
You've taken everything away from me. Does it make you feel good?
If you take everything away at once,
he won't suffer enough to realize what he's done to me.
Then, why do you need me?
You'll make him vicious.
And that'll make me strong.
So that if he ask me to forgive him and think about our past,
I won't back down.
What has he done to you?
Kwang Soo, find out what Yoo Jung did
and who she met this week.
Ja Yeong.
Do we have any food?
You haven't come home for 2 days, and now you just come back and ask me for food?
Tell me what happened.
I'm hungry.
I need to eat first.
I need energy to do things.
I made bean curd soup.
Come in.
By the end of the year, we'll finish the renewal of the check-in system at our branches worldwide.
The facilities of our hotels at home...
I've read related flies.
Then why did you want to see me?
You want to know?
I'm not good at beating around the bush.
What's going on between you and Yoo Jung?
What have you done to her to make her turn her back on you?
If it's not related to business, I'll leave now.
Mr. Ahn.
You were with Kang Yoo Jung on the day of the accident.
You share secrets more precious than life
and now you've turned against each other?
I'm really curious about what happened.
Neither of you want to tell me the reasons behind it.
Kwang Soo!
Yes, sir!
Are you checking into it?
The black box footage will be recovered soon.
Good.
I'll see you at the board meeting.
Se Yeon will be there, right?
Does Se Yeon know about you and Kang Yoo Jung?
I warned you not to see Se Yeon as you wish.
Don't forget that.
I'll introduce you my new parter, who will help me with the new startup,
and the development of King's Restaurant.
I'm Kang Yoo Jung.
Are you qualified to attend a board meeting now?
Mr. Jo isn't familiar with the restaurant menu, so I came along.
Please don't get the wrong ideas.
You said the same thing before.
How else am I supposed to react?
You give me reasons to get the wrong ideas.
What's the real reason for you to stay with Min Hyuk?
Will you excuse me?
Is this what you were talking about?
You want to use Jo Min Hyuk to upgrade your status?
Is that how you made it this far?
We are not like Mr.An and you,
I just need a partner.
You are crazy.
You're well aware of who she is.
If you find out who Mr. Ahn really is, you'll change your mind.
Let's go.
Come to work at my place tomorrow.
Again?
I told you not to question me.
Yes, sir.
Was that good enough?
You should be more resolute,
when stand in front of him.
I will.
Thank you.
What do they want to do?
If he brought her to get your attention,
I guess it worked.
This is very annoying.
If that's what you want,
I'll separate them.
What is this?
We need to prevent it from being published.
What's going on?
Everyone knows about it
except me.
When will my father come back?
Executive Director Im and I will co-sign to get the 20 million dollars from K Capital.
We should stabilize the price of our shares first...
What did my father say?
Why did he go to Germany?
What for?
I can't tell him, yet.
No one could reach him during his operation.
Operation?
How can I know nothing about that as his only son?
While he's absent, you're the head of the K Corporation.
If you knew that, how come you didn't tell me?
The K Hotel.
Buy shares in the K Hotel.
It's my father's first business.
How's my father?
They'll contact me soon.
You have to get back to the hotel right now.
Prove to them that you're the legitimate heir.
That's why my father wanted me to make a profit from the restaurant chain?
Your father and the K Corporation won't fold that easily.
If you find out anything, tell me.
Kang Yoo Jung... She's the one who killed Min Hyuk's girlfriend.
He knows it and still keeps her around.
How hateful they are.
I thought I knew Min Hyuk,
but I'm not so sure now.
He's obsessed with Yoo Jung
like he was with Seo Ji Hee.
Don't you have something to tell me?
Yes.
I told you I once loved someone,
and I want to forget her,
The woman is Kang Yoo Jung.
Do Hoon.
I didn't want others find it out.
In front of me and Min Hyuk,
you've pretended that you didn't know her.
Min Hyuk knew about us all along.
The three of you have made a complete fool out of me.
I didn't mean to,
but I'm guilty that I lied to you.
I'm sorry.
You'sorry?
That's easy.
I didn't know this would happen.
Yoo Jung and I were done long time ago.
The way that Min Hyuk's been treating Yoo Jung...
You're the same.
Men are the same.
I used to hope that you were different.
I was wrong.
Se Yeon!
You've fooled me for such a long time.
Don't make excuses.
I don't want to hear anymore.
Ah.
Drink something warm.
Here you are.
It's hot.
When wer had no work in jail,
do you remember what you said?
What?
If we persist, 1 minute turns into 1 hour,
1 hour turns into 1 month.
No matter how slow it seems to go, time passes.
Everybody was talking about their past...
Hey, all they said about their past were lies.
They did it to pass the time.
I always thought about the future at that time.
I thought thinking about the past seemed silly.
If I think of San and my father...
Stop thinking of something strange.
It's a waste of life to hate other people.
That's the stupidest thing ever.
There are so many people who get away with doing terrible things.
That's strange, right?
That's not fair, isn't it?
The Fried Rice Cake is done, come and eat.
Yoo Jung, what's going on between you and Min Hyuk?
I mean, Do Hoon dumped you, and...
Why don't you just go out with Min Hyuk?
Hey!
You are so idealistic.
Yoo Jung, I heard he's getting married soon.
It's illegal to have a relationship with a married man.
Illegal?
If you know that,
why are you going out with a married man?
Hey! How dare you!
He said he could live without the sun, but not without me.
We're so much in love with each other.
Anyway,
you can't go out with him.
You're involved with him for the wrong reasons.
You won't have a happy ending together.
So what?
We' re not animal.
I don't think he'll go ahead with this arranged marriage.
Besides, Mr. Jo doesn't care about that woman.
Really?
Don't worry. Nothing's going to happen.
Stop pretending.
Then why are you staying with him?
Because you like him, right?
Stop the nonsense!
The rice cake tastes strange.
Remake it.
Come on.
Bring some sugar.
- Just sugar? - Yes.
There was a girl who came to see Yoo Jung.
Lee Hye Jin. She was Yoo Jung's cellmate.
So?
She reported Yoo Jung for maltreating her son.
Three days ago, Ja Yeong went to the police
asking for the surveillance camera footages near Yoo Jung's bakery.
Bakery? When?
It's a parking surveillance camera,
and she got the footage from the day his father went missing.
Her son and her father.
Find her. At all costs.
And bring me that camera footage as well.
Yes, sir.
I once loved someone, that's Kang Yoo Jung.
What's the real reason you're with Min Hyuk?
We're not like you and Mr. Ahn.
I just need a partner.
I thought you just killed someone by mistake,
but you're much worse than that.
Do Hoon told me that you were his girlfriend.
What are you trying to do with these two men?
Sorry, I didn't mean to disturb you.
Yet, you still come to my house.
I have something to do.
I need to pay my debt to Min Hyuk,
and get some things from Do Hoon.
You're sorry, but you're still going to be around?
I'm afraid so.
Okay. Go ahead.
I can get rid of a leech.
So
Why can't we have this profitabe restaurant?
Se Gwang is showing great interest in the King's Restaurant.
This is the only company that we can cash in on
at the moment.
You're selling it to Se Gwang?
Mr. Ahn, who're you working for?
The profits you made so far,
isn't enough to get the board
to permit more investments.
Since when do I need your permission?
The K Hotel shares that you have
don't exceed what Se Yeon and the board have.
All the decisions are made by the board members.
What do you think?
I brought one since you're too busy to come and see it.
She sure is something.
She said she has a debt to pay to Min Hyuk,
and some things to get from you.
Do you still have feelings for her?
No.
Did you mean it
when you said you wanted to forget her?
Yes, I already have.
That's enough. The past is past.
You said you could separate them.
Do it for me.
Thank you for telling me the truth,
You respect me.
Thank you.
It's strange.
You came back till midnight.
I was busy working.
So, what was it that kept you so busy?
Something that concerns both you and me. Our restaurant.
Are you going home with me today?
No! I have work to do.
I'm glad that things between you and Mr. Jo are going well,
but you shouldn't be too obedient.
Do you know that?
- Hae Ri? - Yes. You know?
Since when do you try to sell a company that's still making profits?
Especially to Se Gwang?
I don't think you're qualified to attend this meeting.
- What? - You're dismissed.
You can't attend this meeting.
Ahn Do Hoon!
Let go of me!
Get him out of here.
Yes.
Let go of me, I said let go of me.
I'm Jo Min Hyuk! I'm the owner of this company.
The board meeting... How did it go?
Is that why you came to see me?
Why don't you chsh your shares in and invest in me?
Why should I? We're not even friends.
What's your collateral?
It happens all the time. It'll eventually pass.
When my father finds out what you've been up to...
I can defend myself.
You're the one who's been hanging out with another girl.
That alone could disqualify you from being my fiance..
I'm not like your mother,
I'm not that obedient.
You should know that.
Shin Se Yeon!
Stop yelling at me!
Both you and Kang Yoo Jung are insane.
I'm trying to make you come to your senses before you completely mess up.
You should thank me.
Send Kang Yoo Jung away.
Then, I'll consider your request.
I thought you were desperate.
Don't you ever mention my mother again.
Jae Ha. Where are you?
Why?
I'm going to give you the apology that you've been waiting for.
Hey! Over here!
What are you doing here?
Everything goes well, I'm here to have a drink with my friend.
Friend?
Thanks to you, I made a good friend.
Thank you.
First my father,
Se Yeon and now Jae Ha?
You're something, Ahn Do Hoon!
As you advised, I've been trying to make connections.
I thought you were here to apologize.
Drink up.
And then apologize.
Why didn't you bring that substandard product together with you?
I might consider helping
that tiny restaurant chain of yours.
Jae Ha!
You should've treated me better.
We both don't have friends.
If you're done, you can go. I want to talk to my friend alone.
Even if he takes over your restaurant,
all the employees will keep their jobs.
Tell Yoo Jung not to worry about losing her job.
By the way, I hope your father gets well soon.
You bastard...
You come and go as if you owned the place.
Where is Yoo Jung?
Do you think Yoo Jung is your pet?
Do you think she's standing by for your call?
Where is she?
Stop harassing her. She works late every night.
Why does she have to work that late?
I'm going to report you to the police.
Driver!
What are you doing here?
Sir, the new sauce tastes good.
It goes well with meat and tastes good with salad as well.
I think the customers will like it.
Do you think it'll make a difference?
If the board decides to sell this restaurant,
we're done.
We have to try.
Nothing's been decided, yet.
Do you want to taste it? I think it's good.
Don't smile.
Will you leave me in the end even you smile at me now?
After getting what you want,
you're going to leave me as well.
You said I'll do what you ask me to do.
Until you tell me to leave,
I'll stay with you.
Next on Secret Love.
You're here, do you want to watch something fun with me?
I was with Yoo Jung on that day.
So what?
Kang Yoo Jung! You!
Did Do Hoon do it?
Yoo Jung, you look like you're going to die soon.
I couldn't die, even if I wanted to.
How are you going to revenge while making food in the kitchen?
Happy birthday to you.
Do you want to leave after dinner?
There is no secret in the world, right?
What happened to Yoo Jung’s father... I'll look into it later.